Sheldon 有件事我一直想说
So Sheldon, there's something I've been wanting to talk about
但我知道那是个敏感话题
but I know it's kind of a touchy subject.
好像有什么话题是不敏感的一样
Way to narrow it down to everything.
是什么事?
What is it?
你的生日快到了
Well, your birthday's coming up.
你从不让我们替你庆祝
And you've never let us celebrate it.
我希望今年也许能庆祝一下
And I was hoping maybe this year we could.
我觉得这话题我们可以讨论一下
Oh, I suppose that's a discussion we could have.
那太好了 我是说
Okay, great, I mean,
并不一定要办个大派对什么的
it doesn't have to be a big party or anything.
我只是...
I was just...
他去哪儿了?
Where'd he go?
等... 等等
W... wait a minute.
你一提他的生日 他就消失了?
You mention his birthday and he vanishes?
以前怎么没人告诉我可以这样?
Well, where's that information been this whole time?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第17集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥前排求男票   校对: UUUU后排求女票
翻译: 百年酱油影 波特妹子 無限月讀 舒大卷子 凤梨酥
他在哪儿?
Well, where is he?
Sheldon 你在哪儿?
Sheldon?
我去他房间看看
I'll check his room.
惊喜!
Surprise!
天啊!
Oh, my God!
我只是举例说明
Just one example
生日派对有多可怕
of how birthdays can be terrible.
听着 我们能不能
Now, can we please
结束这个话题 换个新的?
drop this subject and pick a new one?
我提议"在汤变成浓汁前
Yeah, I suggest "how thick can a soup get
最稠能有多稠?"
before it becomes a stew?"
要知道 答案可能让你大吃一惊
You know, the answer, it may surprise you.
我提了这个话题 真对不起
I'm sorry I brought it up.
这话题有什么问题?
Yeah, what is the problem?
是因为觉得自己变老了吗?
Is it about getting older?
拜托 看看我这精致的皮肤
Please, look at this porcelain skin.
简直光彩照人
I'm like a human sink.
但这是你每年一次的专属日啊
But it's the one day a year that's just all about you.
就一次
One day.
没错
Right.
你能告诉我原因吗?
Can you please just tell me why?
好吧
Fine.
你也知道 我有个双胞胎妹妹
As you know, I have a twin sister
她的生日显然和我是同一天
with whom I obviously share a birthday.
每年我们都会办派对
Every year we'd have a party.
我请的人从不会来参加
No one I invited would ever come,
因为他们不喜欢我
because they didn't like me.
别难过了
I'm sorry.
我倒不是很伤心
Oh, that part wasn't so bad.
反正我也不喜欢他们
I didn't like them, either.
但我就没法避免
But then I'd inevitably spend
那一整天都被我妹妹的朋友折磨
the whole day being tortured by my sister's friends.
真可怜
Oh, you poor thing.
我六岁那年 他们跟我说蝙蝠侠会来参加我的派对
When I was six, they told me Batman was coming to my party.
我在门口等了好几个小时
I waited by the door for hours.
结果我看到唯一和蝙蝠侠有关的
Closest thing to Batman I saw was when
就是一只知更鸟飞进了窗户
a robin flew into the window.
知更鸟和蝙蝠侠的伙伴罗宾都是robin
你应该知道现在不会有这些事了吧?
You realize none of those things would happen now?
我知道 但你干嘛在乎
I do, but why do you care
我过不过生日呢?
if I celebrate my birthday at all?
你把我上一个生日变得超级难忘
Well, you made my last birthday so memorable,
我想报答你
I wanted to return the favor.
没错 如果这次
Yeah, if you had
你先办派对 你有很多朋友
a party now, you have plenty of friends
超级想来参加的
that would love to come.
而且我们就住这儿 反正别无选择
And we live here, so we have no choice.
没错
Yeah.
好吧
Very well.
你可以庆祝我的生日 办个派对
You may celebrate my life by throwing a party
准备蛋糕礼物 让它充满赞美和爱
with cake, presents and a shower of admiration and love.
但这样你就欠了我个大人情
But then you owe me big-time.
你想好要送Sheldon
You have any idea what you're getting
什么生日礼物了吗?
Sheldon for his birthday?
他最近痴迷于恐龙
He's been fascinated with dinosaurs lately.
也许我们应该送他块化石
Maybe we could get him a fossil.
别选侏罗纪的东西
Well, just don't get anything Jurassic.
他觉得那一整段时期都被好莱坞承包了
He feels like that whole chunk of time has gone Hollywood.
嘿 听我说
Hey, uh, you know,
他讲了他妹妹骗他说
he told a sad story about how his sister
蝙蝠侠会参加他的生日派对的悲惨故事
tricked him into thinking Batman was coming to his party.
真有趣
That's funny.
我们拿这个骗他吧
Let's do that.
或者我们真的请蝙蝠侠来
Maybe we could get Batman to actually show up.
你是说 找个人扮一下?
You mean, some guy in a lame suit?
是真的蝙蝠侠 Stuart?
Or a real Batman. Hey, Stuart?
你不是有次请了Adam West过来签售吗?
Didn't you try to get Adam West to do a signing here once?
对 但当时行程安排出了点问题
Yeah, but there was kind of a scheduling conflict.
他想知道什么时候能拿到钱
He, uh, wanted to know when he'd get paid.
但我偏不告诉他
And I wouldn't tell him.
能给我他的联系方式吗?
Can I get his contact info?
当然 但提醒你一下
Sure, uh, but just so you know,
他这人特别事儿
he's kind of a diva.
- 是吗?  - 可不呢
- He is?  - Oh, yeah.
不肯坐公交车
Won't take the bus.
不肯自带午餐
He won't pack his own lunch.
还不肯让人在他家沙发上过夜
Won't let you spend the night on his couch.
你觉得派对气球怎么弄?
Okay, so how do you feel about party balloons?
铝箔气球可以有
Uh, Mylar balloons, yes.
乳胶气球不行
Latex balloons, no.
要是水球 那我就瞄准你的车
Water balloons, I will jump off the roof
从楼顶跳下去
and aim for your car.
知道了 那音乐呢?
All right, what about music?
我喜欢游行乐队
I enjoy marching bands
还有西藏的喉音唱法
and Tibetan throat singing.
音乐免了
No music it is.
你喜欢什么蛋糕?
What kind of cake do you like?
我最爱草莓霜的巧克力蛋糕
Well, my favorite is chocolate with strawberry frosting,
三层 如果上面有字的话
three layers, and if there's
不可以全部大写
writing on it, make sure it's not all caps.
我可不想甜点冲我嚷嚷
I don't need my dessert yelling at me.
Adam在电话里怎么样?
Hey, so what was Adam West like on the phone?
人还不错
Uh, nice guy.
但听蝙蝠侠说"别按门铃
But it was a little weird to hear Batman say,
不然我的狗宝宝们会发疯"有点奇怪
"Don't ring the doorbell or my poodles will go crazy."
你知道吗? 他是我最爱的蝙蝠侠
You know, Adam West is my favorite Batman?
那个
Well,
除了迈克尔·基顿和克里斯蒂安·贝尔
after Michael Keaton, Christian Bale
还有乐高大电影里的蝙蝠侠
and Batman from The Lego Movie.
你别跟他说这个
Don't say that to him.
怎么了? 他赢了乔治·克鲁尼
What? He beat out George Clooney.
这很厉害啊
And that's something.
人家可心水克鲁尼呢
Like, I love me some Clooney.
你别再说这句话了
Don't say that to anyone.
谢谢你来帮忙 Stuart
Thank you so much for helping us, Stuart.
哦... 我能被邀请
Oh, I... I was just
就很开心了
glad to be invited.
说实话 我有时候觉得自己不属于这个团体
To be honest, I don't always feel like I'm part of the group.
行了 亲 我们赶时间呢
Okay, sweetie, we're on the clock here.
你能边涂糖霜边自嘲么?
Can you hate yourself and frost at the same time?
嗨 希望我没来得太早
Hello, I hope I'm not too early.
没没 快进
No, no, no. Come on in.
我们容光焕发的准妈妈怎么样啊?
And how is the radiant mommy-to-be?
挺好的
Doing great.
你怀孕了?
Y-You're pregnant?
嗯
Yeah.
听起来像是
Sounds like something
团体成员该知道的事儿啊
a member of the group might know.
生日派对先
Yeah, birthday party first.
自怨派对后
Pity party later.
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
你怎么能把迈克尔·基顿
How can you put Michael Keaton
排在克里斯蒂安·贝尔前面呢?
in front of Christian Bale?
拜托哦
Oh, please.
就连我的狗宝都知道贝尔被过誉了
Even my poodles know Bale's overrated.
谢谢你!
Thank you!
所以我才说基顿是第一
That's why I say Keaton's number one.
他给角色注入了幽默感
He brought a sense of humor to the role.
哦 你们要是考虑幽默感的话
Oh, if you're gonna factor in a sense of humor,
那我就该排第一了
then I should be at the top of the list.
排名应该是我
It should be me,
基顿 基尔默
Keaton, Kilmer,
乐高 贝尔
Lego, Bale,
还有小白脸克鲁尼
and that pretty boy Clooney.
真的吗?
Really?
你在贝尔前面?
You're ahead of Bale?
那个把"我是蝙蝠侠"
The man who personified the words,
说成招牌的男人
"I'm Batman."
我从来不用说自己是蝙蝠侠
I never had to say I'm Batman.
我出现
I showed up.
大家就知道我是蝙蝠侠
People knew I was Batman.
不论去哪... 电视节目
Everywhere I went... on the TV show,
商场开业...
mall openings...
朱丽叶·纽玛的别墅
Julie Newmar's bungalow.
我信了... 你比贝尔强
I'm sold... you're ahead of Bale.
还有一个我应该排名靠前的原因
There's another reason I should be higher on the list.
其他这些家伙
All those other guys
演出服里都有垫东西假扮肌肉
had muscles built into their costumes.
我的演出服里
All I had in my Batsuit
可是100%如假包换的优质肌肉男West
was 100%, grade-A West.
ben affleck 新的蝙蝠侠扮演者
反正大家统一意见都不看好Affleck就好了?
Can we just all agree we're worried about Affleck?
- 好的  - 当然了
- Sure.  - Yeah, of course.
Affleck是谁?
What's an Affleck?
真的有必要让我离开住的地方吗?
Is there a reason I had to leave my own apartment?
他们只是想让你第一眼
Well, I think they just want you to see it
看见的时候就已经是都装扮好了的
for the first time all decorated.
那该由谁来告诉他们做法完全不对呢?
But who's gonna tell them they're doing it wrong?
我肯定他们会要你讲点儿什么的
Well, I'm... I'm sure they'll ask you to give a speech,
那时你就能好好把握机会了
and that's when you just tear 'em a new one.
不得不说...
Have to say, you...
你穿这套衣服真帅
you do look good in that suit.
谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
或许待会儿我可以...
Maybe later I'll, uh...
出生时穿的(裸体)
看你穿生日套装
get to see you in your birthday suit.
可这就是我的生日套装啊
But this is my birthday suit.
你脑子抽了?
Are you having a stroke?
那种事情
Because that's the kind of thing
只会毁掉生日派对的气氛
that just ruins a birthday party.
老妈 我很意外你大老远地
So, Mother, I'm surprised you came all this way
跑来参加Sheldon的生日派对
for Sheldon's birthday.
我愿意来
Oh, I was happy to.
他参加了我的60大寿
He did come to my 60th.
你还办了60大寿呢?
Oh. You had a party for your 60th?
没怎么大操大办
Oh, I wouldn't call it a party.
就几个经常来往的朋友
Just a few close friends.
还有你姐姐和哥哥
And your sister and brother.
公平点讲 我们在拉斯维加斯结婚时
You know, to be fair, we did get married in Vegas
也没有邀请她
and didn't invite her.
我还没为你贴心的这么做谢过你呢 宝贝
And I never did thank you for that, dear.
噢
Oh.
Penny说大家伙都来了 你准备好了吗?
Penny says everyone's there. Are you ready?
准备好了
I am.
- 等等  - 你还好吗?
- Oh. Wait.  - Are you all right?
我只是...有点发晕
No, I just... I got a little light-headed.
你要歇会儿吗?
Oh, d-do you need a minute?
不用了
No.
既然我能走过
No, if I can walk past that pet shop
窗口有鹦鹉的宠物店 我想这个我也能挺过去
with the parrot in the window, I suppose I can do this.
生日快乐!
Happy birthday!
说点什么!
Speech! Speech!
来啊 Sheldon 说点什么
Come on, Sheldon, say something.
呃...
Uh, um...
感谢大家都能过来
uh, thank you all so much for coming.
谢谢你 Beverly
Uh, Beverly.
还有你 Wil Wheaton
Wil Wheaton.
Adam West 也不知道为啥来了
Adam West, for some reason.
蝙蝠侠终于来参加你的生日派对了
Batman finally came to your party.
生日快乐 Sherman
Happy birthday, Sherman.
谢谢
Thank you.
这些都太贴心了
This is all so thoughtful.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我还是有报酬的 对吧?
I still get paid, don't I?
我最好进去跟他谈谈
Okay, I'd better go in there and talk to him.
你不觉得该由我进去和他谈吗?
Well, don't you think I'm the one who should go in?
没别的意思 可我认识他很长时间了
No offense, but I've known the guy a really long time.
我也 你知道
Well, I've, you know,
见过他赤条条的样子
seen him without pants on.
还是没别的意思 我也见过
Again, no offense, but so have I.
他见过我赤条条的样子
Well, he's seen me without pants on.
还是这么说...
Again, no...
够了 太恶心了
Okay, this is ridiculous.
Sheldon 还好吗?
Sheldon?
我能进来吗?
Can I come in?
你咋知道我没在上厕所?
How do you know I'm not using the facilities?
因为即使我无数次的取消订阅
Because you e-mail me your bathroom schedule once a week,
可你还是每周都发邮件
even though I've clicked unsubscribe,
告诉我你如厕时间表
like, a thousand times.
所以...
So...
到底怎么了?
what's going on?
我也不明白
I don't know.
我看了看房子
I-I looked around the room,
看到了大伙的笑脸还有礼物
and I saw all the faces and the presents,
就觉得...太过了
and it... it was just too much.
我明了了
I get that.
你愿意只叫几个人进来吗?
Hey, you want to just bring a few people in here?
Wil Wheaton站澡缸里
You know, Wil Wheaton in the bathtub,
蝙蝠侠坐马桶上
Batman on the toilet.
就像有史以来最古怪的动漫展
It'll be like the weirdest Comic-Con ever.
我知道你们花了很多心思办这个
I know that you worked hard to put this together.
抱歉我搞糟了
I'm sorry I'm ruining it.
别啊 你没有搞糟
Oh, pl... You're not ruining it.
某一刻 Raj 还想让大家
Look, at some point, Raj will try to get everyone
跳太空舞步
to do the Electric Slide.
那才会毁了派对
Now, that will ruin it.
我不觉得我现在可以去外面
I don't think I can go back out there.
可以啊
That's fine.
我讨厌你的妹妹和她的朋友们
You know, I hate that your sister and her friends
过去经常折磨你
used to torture you.
但我更讨厌
But what I hate even more
如果当时我在 我也会和她们一起折磨你
is, if I was there, I would have tortured you, too.
你这段"鼓舞人心"的话 也是在折磨我
Based on this pep talk, I'd say you're still doing it.
我的意思是
My point is,
曾几何时 我不可能会和
there was a time I never would've been friends
你这样的人成为朋友 但是现在...
with someone like you, and now...
你是我最喜欢的人
you are one of my favorite people.
所以 如果你想
So, if what you need is
在厕所度过你的生日
to spend your birthday in a bathroom,
我很高兴可以陪你一起
I'm happy to do it with you.
那大家会觉得我很奇怪的
Well, everyone will think I'm weird.
亲 你就是很奇怪
Sweetie, you are weird.
大家都知道你奇怪
Everyone knows you're weird,
但他们还是来了
but they're all still here
因为他们是如此的关心你
because they care about you so much.
喂
Hello.
有人需要整理一下发型
Some of us need to check our hair
因为他可能有机会泡到Leonard的妈妈
because we might have a shot with Leonard's mother.
- Leonard  - 你好
- Leonard.  - Hey.
好久不见
It's been a while.
Leslie.
Leslie
我都不记得我们上次讲话时什么时候了
I can't remember the last time we talked.
好多事情变了
So much has changed.
是吗?
Has it?
是啊 Penny和我结婚了
Yeah, uh, um, Penny and I got married.
哇哦 恭喜啊
Wow, congratulations.
你要知道 实际上
You know, actually,
我以为你会永远和Sheldon住在一起
I thought you'd be living with Sheldon forever.
是啊 呃...
Yeah, well...
下回聊
Don't be a stranger.
好的 大家伙儿
Okay, everybody,
Sheldon要出来了
Sheldon is gonna come back out,
但我觉得他还是有点尴尬
but I think he's a little embarrassed,
所以我们表现的格外友好一点 好吗?
so let's all be extra nice, okay?
你干嘛看着我?
What are you looking at me for?
我是个圣人
I'm a saint.
但在床上的时候是个罪人
But a sinner in the sack.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
我...
I-I...
我对我刚才的行为表示抱歉
I'd like to apologize for my behavior.
希望没有扫大家的兴
I hope it hasn't put a damper on the party.
大家玩得高兴
So, just, please, enjoy yourselves.
那就好
That's good.
这失控的好快
Oh, this is quickly getting out of hand.
如果可以
If I may,
我提议举杯
I-I'd like to propose a toast.
谢谢大家今晚的到来
Um, thank you all for coming tonight.
我知道
I know it's customary
寿星收礼物是传统
for the birthday boy to receive presents,
但我觉得当他出生时
but I feel like I got the greatest gift
我收到了最好的礼物
the day he was born.
哇哦
Aw.
- 听听  - 干杯
- Hear, hear.  - Cheers.
Amy 说的真好
Amy, that was lovely.
这好有趣
this is fun.
再来
Let's do more.
其他人说些关于我的好话
Someone else say something wonderful about me.
Sheldon 我不觉得大家...
Sheldon, I don't think everyone...
Wolowitz 好极了 大家听Wolowitz说
Wolowitz, perfect. Everyone listen to Wolowitz.
好吧 呃
Okay, then, uh,
Sheldon啊
Sheldon,
我们认识彼此有很长时间了
we've known each other a long time.
和你一起工作 做你的朋友
And it is a pleasure to work with you
都是很愉快的
and call you my friend.
有点普通 继续想 待会儿轮回来
Little generic. Keep thinking. We'll circle back.
Wil Wheaton 你说
Wil Wheaton, go.
Sheldon 我知道我们的关系有起伏
Sheldon, I know that we've had our ups and downs,
但我可以很真诚地说
but I can honestly say
我的生命因为有你
that my life is so much more interesting
而变得更精彩
because you are in it.
或许我们的相遇是因为你是星际迷航的粉丝
We may have met because you are a fan of Star Trek.
但我现在已经成为Sheldon Cooper的粉丝
But I have become a fan of Sheldon Cooper.
《星际迷航》中瓦肯人的祝福手势
生生不息 繁荣昌盛 兄弟
Live long and prosper, buddy.
生日快乐
And happy birthday.
干杯
Cheers.
你应该这样说 Wolowitz
That's how you do it, Wolowitz.
现在我们知道
Now you see
为什么他出名而你没有
why he's famous and you're not.
嘿 Sheldon
Sheldon,
我知道你在未来一定会变得更好
I know the future holds great things for you,
我们都很期待看到未来更好的你
and we all can't wait to see what they are.
生日快乐 亲爱的
Happy birthday, dear.
干杯
Cheers.
谁给动物管理局打个电话吧
Someone call Animal Control.
有头美洲豹出来野了
There's a cougar on the loose.
Barry 别闹了
Barry, stop.
讲真 Barry 你够了
Seriously, Barry, stop.
甘地曾经说过
And it was Gandhi who said,
"珍惜生命
"Live as if you were to
"如同死亡即将来临
"die tomorrow.
"热爱学习
"Learn as if you were to live
如同你有永恒的生命"
forever."
而Sheldon Cooper曾经说过 "你快点说
And it was Sheldon Cooper who said "Let's speed this up.
还有好多人等着说话呢"
A lot of people want to talk"
以前 我大概会说点不好听的
Uh, in the past, I would've said something obnoxious,
比如说 "生日快乐啊 蠢货"
like, "Happy birthday, dumbass".
不过今年我准备换换样
But I'm not gonna do it.
咱们都成熟了不少
You and I have both grown a lot,
能再次见到你们 我真的很开心
and it's just so nice to see you all again.
所以...
So...
生日快乐 Sheldon
happy birthday, Sheldon.
谢谢
Oh.
可是你知道我最讨厌的就是变化 重新说
Oh, now, you know I hate change. Say it.
生日快乐 蠢货!
Happy birthday, dumbass!
生日快乐 年轻人
Happy birthday, young man.
如果你们今天见到我很开心的话
And if any of you have enjoyed seeing me here today,
我还可以出席漫展
I'm also available for Comic-Cons,
单身趴 犹太受戒仪式...
bachelor parties, bar mitzvahs...
我想不到还有什么别人没说过的了
I can't think of anything to say that hasn't already been said.
这杯敬你 Sheldon
So, here's to you, Sheldon.
干杯 干杯
Hear, hear. Hear, hear.
谢谢你 Bernadette
Thank you, Bernadette.
你说的太好了
That was perfect.
神马? 你在逗我笑?
What? You gotta be kidding me?
Sheldon 我们认识的时间太长了
Sheldon, we've been together so long,
我都想不出来 我生活中没有你是什么样子的了
it's hard to remember a time you weren't in my life.
真的 我努力想过
And believe me, I try.
你给我带来了欢乐
You make me laugh.
你帮我成为了更好的科学家
You make me a better scientist.
你也会让我抓狂
You make me crazy.
我绝不仅仅把你当做室友
You're more than just my roommate,
我已经把你当做亲兄弟了
you're my brother.
谢谢
Thank you.
生日快乐
Happy birthday, buddy.
干杯
Cheers.
谢谢 你们... 你们说的都太好了
Thank you. That... that was wonderful.
等一下 等一下
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Stuart还没说呢
Stuart didn't get to speak.
哦 好吧 呃...
Oh, oh, okay. Um...
那个 Sheldon
Uh, Sheldon,
我一直都觉得 从来没人注意我
I've spent most of my life feeling invisible,
不过和你们在一起...
but having you and everyone...
嘿 你们快来看
Hey, everybody, listen up.
说的不错
You nailed it.
有个人不能来这里
We've got someone who couldn't be here
不过他很想亲口对你说
but really wanted to wish you
生日快乐
a happy birthday.
你好啊 Sheldon
Hello, Sheldon.
霍金教授
Professor Hawking.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you.
太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
我真没想到你...
I can't believe you're...
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you.
哦 你是在唱歌啊 对不起
Oh, you're singing. Well, I'm sorry.
祝亲爱的Sheldon生日快乐
Happy birthday, dear Sheldon.
呃 霍金教授
Uh, Professor Hawking,
你能不能等一下
if you just give us one second,
等我们把蜡烛点好 然后就可以一起唱了
we'll light the candles, and we can all sing together.
打断了我这动人的歌喉 不跟你计较了
I was crushing it, but all right.
趁他们准备蛋糕
Okay, while they get the cake,
我想说 Sheldon
Sheldon, I just want to say,
不来个大大的熊抱
I hope you didn't think you were gonna get through tonight
你是过不去今晚的
without a hug.
你知道我以前有多痛恨拥抱
You know, I used to hate these hugs.
现在 只是觉得很烦人而已了
Now they're just extremely irritating.
你准备好了我们就开始吧 霍金教授
Ready when you are, Professor Hawking.
一 二 开始...
And a one, and a two...
# 祝你生日快乐 #
# Happy birthday to you #
# 祝亲爱的Sheldon生日快乐 #
# Happy birthday, dear Sheldon #
# 祝你生日快乐 #
# Happy birthday to you. #
...快乐
...to you.
好了 你们谁送我回家?
So, who's taking me home?